var data=[
  { 
  "Qid":1,"question":"Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array?","opt":{"opt1":"changeOrder()","opt2":"reverse()","opt3":"sort()","opt4":"append()"},"ans":"reverse()"
  },
  { 
  "Qid":2,"question":" Which built-in method returns the string representation of the number's value?","opt":{"opt1":"toValue()","opt2":"toNumber()","opt3":"toString()","opt4":"none"},"ans":"toString()"
  },

	{ 
  "Qid":3,"question":"Which built-in method returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location?","opt":{"opt1":"substr()","opt2":"getSubstring()","opt3":"slice()","opt4":"none"},"ans":"substr()"
	},
  
	{ 
  "Qid":4,"question":"Which of the following function of String object returns the character at the specified index?","opt":{"opt1":" charAt()","opt2":"charCodeAt()","opt3":"concat()","opt4":"indexOf()"},"ans":"charAt()"
	},
  { 
  "Qid":5,"question":"Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be italic, as if it were in an <i> tag?","opt":{"opt1":"fixed()","opt2":"fontcolor()","opt3":"fontsize()","opt4":" italics()"},"ans":" italics()"
},
  { 
  "Qid":6,"question":"Which built-in method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array?","opt":{"opt1":"last()","opt2":"put()","opt3":"push()","opt4":"none"},"ans":"push()"
	},

  { 
  "Qid":7,"question":"react is two way binding..?","opt":{"opt1":"yes","opt2":"no","opt3":"with flux only","opt4":"with redux only"},"ans":"no"
  }
  ,	
  { 
  "Qid":8,"question":"Which of the following function of Array object adds and/or removes elements from an array? ","opt":{"opt1":"toSource()","opt2":"sort()","opt3":"splice()","opt4":"unshift()"},"ans":"splice()"
	},

  { 
  "Qid":9,"question":"what is curenet version of java script.?","opt":{"opt1":"2.3","opt2":"2.9","opt3":"2.8","opt4":"none"},"ans":"none"
  }
  ,
  { 
  "Qid":10,"question":"Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number?","opt":{"opt1":" toString()","opt2":"toFixed()","opt3":"toLocaleString()","opt4":"toPrecision()"},"ans":"toString()"
	}

	
]


export default data;
